[音乐]
[MUSIC]
&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：那么我们对发电机的感觉如何？让我们尝试一下练习和
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: So how are we feeling about generator Let's try an exercise and
看看我们对发电机的感觉。
see how we're feeling about generators.
我们要再去一次，再回到井里去一次。
We're gonna go one more time, deep back in the well one more time.
我们已经有的这个并行进行三个调用的运行示例
This running example that we've had of making the three calls in parallel and
排序他们的反应。
sequencing their responses.
我迫不及待地想让你看到发电机的解决方案有多酷。
I cannot wait for you to see how cool the solution is with generators.
这对我来说是最难做的事，再等十分钟你再试一试，
This is the hardest thing for me to do, to wait ten more minutes while you try it,
因为我现在只想给你看。
cuz I just wanna show it to you right now.
但我想给你一个机会来练习思考发电机的方式
But I wanna give you a chance to practice thinking about generators the way I
刚才说的，试着看看你能不能把你的大脑包围起来。
just talked about, try to see if you can get your brain wrapped around.
我会怎么做并行的事情，然后等待
How would I do things in parallel, but then wait for
对他们的输出进行排序？
them to sequence their output?
所以试着用发电机练习七。
So try exercise seven with a generator.
您可以使用序列来运行它，因为这非常方便，
You can use a sequence to run it cuz that's pretty convenient,
它已经包含在那里了。
it's already included there for you.
最后五个或
The last five or
六张幻灯片应该有足够的信息来帮助你。
six slides should have more than enough info to help you with that.